http://www.rlc-callender.com/privacy-policy/

PrivacyPrivacy PolicyRLC Engineering Group is committed to processing personal information about its customers in ways that comply with its legal and regulatory obligations, and ensuring that we are clear with customers about how their personal information is used. This Policy explains how we use any personal information we may collect about you when you use our websites; or when you use or are a recipient of our services.RLC is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.Information collectionRLC Engineering Group may ask you to submit personal information – for example your name, your phone number and email address. Where you voluntarily choose to give us your personal details the personal data you provide will be used exclusively for providing you with the information or service you have requested.Automatically collected dataWe log visitor's domain and IP address automatically; this information does not identify you as an individual, but only the computer that is being used to view the site. This data is used to see where the site is being used globally to better understand site usage, so that we can improve our service. We do not link information automatically logged by such means with personal data about specific individuals.Information Sharing and DisclosureWe will only send personally identifiable information about you to other organisations when we have your consent. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.Data ProtectionWhen you supply personal information to RLC Engineering Group we have a legal obligation to you in how we protect and use that information. We must, for example, tell you when we are collecting such data and why, and if we intend to pass this information on to a third party. You must give us your permission if you wish us to pass your details on to a third party partner. You have the legal right to request a copy of any information that we hold about you.Company Registration No. 1195730 (England).  Registered Office: 3rd Floor , 1 Trinity Park, Bickenhill Lane , Birmingham , B37 7ES
Cookies
This website uses cookies as described in our Cookie policy. To see what cookies we serve and set your own preferences, please use your web browser's settings. Otherwise, if you agree to our use of cookies, please continue to use our website.
Close
Close
SALES OF OVER
£140M
P/A
we employ over
1000
People
established in
1955
Serving Customers Globally
Cookies
This website uses cookies as described in our Cookie policy. To see what cookies we serve and set your own preferences, please use your web browser's settings. Otherwise, if you agree to our use of cookies, please continue to use our website.
Close
Close
